Finding Aid for the Elizabeth Vann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Twenty-fifth We dding Anniversary Correspondence, Autographs, DAH, Genealogy, Autobiography, Vanderbilt University
  - Folder 16: The Alumnus - Vanderbilt University: Reunions, Quinks (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - June 23 (Box 28)
    - 1974: Aug.13,(1) (Box 28)
    - 1975: Oct. (Box 28)
    - 1976: Apr.8 (Box 28)
    - June 3,30 (Box 28)
  - Folder 16, continued: (Box 28)
    - Vanderbilt University, Student Services.1974: Jan. (Box 28)
    - Vanderbilt University, Treasurer. 1977: Jan,21 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence from Virginia Commonwealth Corporation. 1973: Sept,18 (Box 28)
  - Folder 17: The Vanderbilt Family at Vanderbilt, 1973 (2) newspaper clippings (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - List of descendants of Commorore Cornelius Vanderbilt (Box 28)
    - Centennial Service of Commoration, 100th Anniversary of the Founding of Vanderbilt University. 1975: Mar.17 (Box 28)
  - Folder 18: Vanderbilt University Reunion, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Report of the Alumni Association Program (Box 28)
    - Clipping from The Tennessean. 1976: May 30 (Box 28)
    - Elizabeth’s account of the reunion (Box 28)
    - Letter from Bill Meadows, Vanderbilt University, 1975: Oct.9 (Box 28)
  - **Folder 19: Vanderbilt University: Correspondence from Alexander (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Heard, Chancellor (Box 28)
    - 1971: Mar.20 (Box 28)
    - 1974: May ? (Box 28)
    - 1975: Nov.17 (Box 28)
    - 1976: Dec. ? (Box 28)
    - 1977: Feb.23 (Box 28)
  - Folder 20: Vanderbilt University: Clippings about Alexander Heard (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Folder 21: Vanderbilt University: Correspondence from Robert A. McGaw (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - 1970: Nov.3 (Box 28)
    - 1973: May 31 (Box 28)
  - Folder 22: Vanderbilt University: Correspondence from Dean Madison Sarratt (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - (2)cards n.d. (Box 28)
    - 1969: Jan.22 (Box 28)
    - 1973: July 23 (Box 28)
  - ***Folder 23: Vanderbilt University: Office of Alumni & Development, Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - From: Alexander, David (2)n.d. (Box 28)
    - 1973: June 22; July 20,23,i (Box 28)
    - Oct.30; Nov.5,20 (Box 28)
    - 1974: Jan.30; Feb.28 (Box 28)
    - Oct.29; Nov.19, 21 (Box 28)
    - Nov. 19(to Henry Svo.nl (Box 28)
    - Dec.24 (Box 28)
    - 1975: Feb.20,24; Mar.3 (Box 28)
    - Nov.24 (Box 28)
    - 1976: Jan.23; May 31 (Box 28)
    - June 10; May 19 (Box 28)
    - From: Patterson, Tom 1964: May 22 (Box 28)
    - From: Smith, Jerry II. 1973: May 1 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence from Elizabeth: (Box 28)
    - 1964: May 27 (to Tom Patterson). 1973: Nov.3(to David 1974: Mar.13(to David Alexander) (Box 28)
  - Folder 24: Vanderbilt University: Friends of the Library Invitation, 1976 (Box 24)
    - Correspondence from: (Box 28)
    - Grisham, Frank P. 1976: Oct.26 (Box 28)
    - Wills, Jesse E. 1974: Oct.17 (Box 28)
  - Folder 25: Dr. William B. Bean: Article and Correspondence Article: “The Public Interest in Medicine” (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence from William Bean to Elizabeth’ 1973: Aug.9; Sept.18,26; 1974: May 3,14. Oct.12; Nov.20 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence from William Bean to Felix Vann 1973: Aug.24; Sept.5 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence from Elizabeth to William Bean Aug.3; 1973: Sept.11,21; Oct.29 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence from Felix Vann to William Bean 1973: Sept.l (Box 28)
  - **Add to Folder 19 - Correspondence from Elizabeth to Alexander Heard: 1963: May 4» 14; June 6; July 9. 1977: Feb.8. (Box 28)
  - ***Add to Folder 23 - Correspondence from: (Box 28)
    - The Divinity School, Dean William C. Finch. 1964: Apr.22(to Roscoe White (Box 28)
    - Ann Ozier 1968: July 18(Jeff Carr) (Box 28)
  - *Add to Folder 13 - Correspondence from: (Box 28)
    - Harry J, Lemley 1962: Aug.10, 22; Sept.3. (Box 28)
    - Belle Boyd: Southern St>v of the Shenandoah. Laura Virginia Hale. (Box 28)
- Elizabeth and Eugene Vann: Forty-Fifth Wedding Anniversary Trip to Europe, Oct.29, 1952-June 1953
  - Trip expenses (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Post cards (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Diary of trip (2 copies) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - International driver’s licenses (2) (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Post cards (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Expense lists (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence about car (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to Family about Trip, 1952: Oct.-Dec. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 1952: Oct.22( Lucy) (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Nov.5 (All)
    8 (Suzanne & Henry)
    9 (All)
    10(11.11)
    13(All)
    16(All)
    19(11.11)
    20(Felix from Dad)
    2l(Sister)
    26(All)
    Dec.5-
    7 (All)
    15-16(All)
    2l(Girls)
    23(All)
    23(Felix from Dad)
    29(Felix from Mom)
    29(Dr. Balze from Elizabeth)
  - Correspondence to Family about Trip, 1953, Jan.-Mar. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 1953: Jan.3(All) (Box 29, Folder 4)
    9(Felix from Mom)
    10(All)
    11(Saidee Jarrell)
    14(Felix from Mom)
    15(Sister)
    20(All)
    20(Felix from Mom)
    28(All)
    Feb.3(All)
    19(all)
    19( Fel ix from Mom)
    19(Lucy)
    25(All)
    Har.6(AJ.l)
    12(Sister)
    12(Felix from Mom)
    12(Felix from Dad)
    12(All)
    19(All)
    25(Sister)
    30(All)
  - Correspondence to Family about Trip, 1953: Apr.-June (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 1953: Apr.4(Felix from Mom) (Box 29, Folder 5)
    10(Sister & All)
    14(Sister)
    24(All)
    30 (Felix, Dorothea, and Richard)
    May 6(Felix & Dorothea)
    8(All)
    18(Felix & Dorothea)
    23(Felix & Dorothea)
    27(Sister)
    29(Felix & Dorothea)
    June 1(Felix from Mom)
    l-4(All)
    7(Sister)
    8(Felix from Mom)
    18(Felix from Mom)
- Correspondence with Paul Showers, New York Times, about the European Trip. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - From Paul Showers to Elizabeth: 1952: Dec.23 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    1952: Dec.23
    1953: May 11; (l)n.d.; July 24; Aug.29.
    1955: Aug.ll
  - From Paul Showers to Margaret Dixon: (Box 29, Folder 6)
    1953: Feb.27; May 1,6.
  - Fan mail to Elizabeth: (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Baird, Julia Dale 195?: May 3
    Baird, Warner G. 195:?: July 17
    Esar, Mrs. Evan 195?: Jan. 5
    Hoffman, Huth P. 195?: June 27; July 9
    Key(?), Marshall 195?: May 5
    Newman, s. 195?: Hay 3
    Scheerer, Jeanette 195?: May 5
  - From Elizabeth to Paul Showers: (Box 29, Folder 6)
    1952: Nov.ll
    1953: Jan.19; July 8(to Paul Freidlander)
- Correspondence concerning Publication of Notes from European Trip (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - To Elizabeth from: (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Doubleday & Company, Inc. 1955: Jan.24; Feb.17
    Journal of Living. 1955: Mar.16
    Lifetime Living. 1953: Jan.16
  - From Elizabeth: (Box 29, Folder 7)
    1953: n.d.(to Sister)
    1953: Feb.ll(to Lifetime Living)
    1953: Aug.15(to Travel Magazine)
- Newspaper Articles about European Trip (Box 29)
  - New York Times. n.d. “Second Honeymoon in Europe” (4copies) (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - New York Times. May 3, 1953. “Second Report on a Leisurely Tour of Europe” (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - New York Times. Hay 26, 1953. “Couple Tours Europe on Four Dollars a Day” (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - ? n.d. “Mrs. Vann Tells of European Trip in New York Times” (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Articles by Elizabeth about European Trip (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - “About Wayside Inns in Spain” (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - “Cost of Our Winter Holiday in Spain” (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - “Guides and Their Uses” (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - “Motoring in Spain” (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - “We Kept Within Our Budget” (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - “Second Honeymoon” - Article About 45th Anniversary Trip to Europe, 1952-1953, (3 drafts) (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - “Home Again” - Last Chapter of Diary, 45th Anniversary Trip to Europe, 1952-1953, (4 drafts) (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Diary and Engagement Books (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Passports (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Golden Wedding Anniversary, 1958: Elizabeth and Eugene Vann (Box 30)
  - Golden Wedding Anniversary Guest Book (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - (l)color negative of Elizabeth and Eugene (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - (2)poems (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Invitation (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Thank you from Hospital Building Fund (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Bergen Evening Record, 1958: May 26 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - The Birmingham News, 1958: June 9 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Englewood Press-Journal, 1958: May 8,22,29; June 12 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Nashvil le Banner, 1958: June 18 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Newark Evening News, 1958: May 23 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - The Tennessean, 1958: June 18 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Vanderbilt Alumnus, Vol.43, No.6, July-Aug., 1958 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - “The Gathering of the Clan for the Golden Wedding of Eugene and Elizabeth Denny Vann” (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Contributions to the Englewood Hospital Association in Honor of Elizabeth and Eugene (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - (168) contributions (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - (22) letters from Nelson R. Henson, Administrator, May 2, 1958 - May 31, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Anniversary Correspondence - 1958 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Cards with flowers and notes from: (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Davis, Anne
    Farrell, Hermon & Elizabeth
    Gautier, Mabel
    Gual, Francisco Garcia
  - Letters (A-L) from: (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Enid
    Howard & Marjorie
    - Adams, Ruth (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Alden, Rose
      Alexander, Ralph
      Arnan, Henry
      Audenio, Dorris Lux
    - Baur, Alice & Gus(2) (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Baudwin, Travee
      Betts, Dorothy & Manley
      Bodet, Robert G.
      Bowerman, Walter G.
      Burke, Irene
    - Carmely, Shulawit & Abraham (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Carriker, John G.
      Caswell, Ruth
      Cheyney, Christine
      Clark, Daisy
      Cline, Grace & Bob
      (1) ?
      Cline, Mary Jane Blue
      Coe, Alice Stanley
      Cregut, May & Peter
    - Davis, Anne (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Davis, Helen L.(2)
      Davis, Watson
      Delany, Ida H.
      Denhardt, Eleanor H.
      Denney, Frank O.
      Denny, Ann
      Denny, Collins & Rebecca(2)
      Denney, J.L.P.
      Denny, Mary Bell
      Divine, Amy
      Dubois, Kathryn
    - Eckert, Helen (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Ellis, Dorothy
      Eleazer, Peggy Fleming
      Ester, Elvira Tucker
    - Farwell, Herman & Elizabeth (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Firestone, Mary Libby
      Fitch, Hugh
      Fletcher, Walter Robert & Monique
      Frantz, Evalin Brown
    - Gautier, Mabel (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Gilbert, Alpha
      Girard, Carlos V. & Florence
      Glaser, Paul
      Gorham, Mary Tucker
      Gual, Francisco “Pancho” Garcia
      Gudgeon, George & Edie
      Guernsey, Grace
      Gunther, Maude C.
    - Hammond, Frances H. (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Hare, David & Louise
      Harrell, Costen
      Haveland, Esther
      Heath, Betty Loundes
      Hemen(?), Tom & Oakley
      Hill, Bessie Fite
      Hill, Roscoe R.
      Hilty, Rose Vann(Mrs. Everett)
      Hippolyte, Dominique
      Hixson, Arthur & Edetha
      Hotchner, Marjorie
      Hoyler, Bertha N.
      Huffman, Charles Herbert
      Hutchinson, Viola L.
    - Igbwad, Rosemary (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Jackson, Isabel (Box 30, Folder 4)
      James, Gertrude G.
      Jarrell, Saidee(2)
      Johnson, ?
    - Kiehan, Marie (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Kiehl, Robert & Mary Virginia(2)
      King, Portia Showalter
      Kingsbury, Helen
      Kiphuth, Delaney & Janet
      Knox, Betty Baur
      Kyler, Agnes T.
    - Lacon(?), Cesar (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Lasky, Charles & Elsie
      Lee, Edith
      Leslie, Elizabeth & Jay
      LeSourd, Mr.&Mrs. Gilbert
      Lewis, Berneita & Don Carlos
      Lopez, Frank (Francisco E.) (2)
      Lothrop, Marguerita
      Lowe, Bessie Craig(2)
      Lowndes, Lucien C.
  - Incoming Anniversary Correspondence - 1958 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Letters (M-W) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    MacBain, Amy(2)
    Mariconda, Margaret
    Marsh, May Baker(2)
    Marson, Mollie
    Martin, Amelia B.
    Mercereau, Helen
    Merrill, Edith & Walter
    Meyer, Suzanne & Henry
    Mills, Lillian & George
    Miller, Lucille N.
    Mohair, Annie Laurie
    Moor, David H.(2)
    Moore, Clara L.
    Moore, Elizabeth
    Morgan, E.
    Motte(?), M.F.
    - Noyes, Anna (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - O’Hearn, Katherine (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Oliver, Freda E.
    - Parajon, Swelina & Mario (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Parker, Jane & Charlie
      Partridge, Cora
      Payne, Elizabeth C.
      Pearce, Lorene V.
      Petzinger, Lambert
      Philips, Helen
      Pinkhar, Lena
      Pomar, I.C.
      Popper, Irene Ellis
      Pontius, Miller H.
      Puckett, Mary
    - Rawill, R. (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Roach, W.J.
      Rosenberry, Bessie& John
      Rothrock, Katharine
    - Salathe, Beryl (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Scales, Fannie Mae
      Schmidt, Wolfgang
      Schneider, C. Conrad
      Schulat, Elsr
      Shedd, Cornelia B.
      Simmons, Fannie Vann
      Slosson, Lucy
      Smith, Alfred H.(2)
      Smoot, Leila M.
      Soldau, Louise V.
      Stanley, Thomas & Dorothea
      Stickle, Fred
      Stokes, Julia
      Stover, Nellie
      Swenson, Mary K.
      Sylvester, Mildred Loring
    - Teague, Florence (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Thompson, Anne II.
      Thornburgh, Fay
      Threlkeld, Aubrey M.
      Tiffany, Mabel A.
      Turner, Elizabeth Montoll
    - Vann, F. Young & Kack(2) (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Vann, Harold. & Francos
      Vann, Joel (2)
      Vann, Monroe & Madeline
      Vann, Sam
      Vaughn, Ruby
    - Ward, Emma (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Ward, Hannah & Ralph
      White, Allen B.
      White, Collins Denny, Jr.
      White, Edith
      Wilcox, Robert & May
      Williams, Elizabeth P.
      Williams, John W.(2)
      Wilson, Anne & Dudley
      Winfree, Lou White
      Woods, Ethel S.(3)
      Wuellner, Wilhelm & Flora May
      Wyckoff, Christobel C.
      Wyckoff, William
- Incoming Anniversary Correspondence - 1958 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Letters, First Name Only (Box 30, Folder 6)
    Anne
    Christine
    Dave & Louise
    Dot
    Cousin Sliem(?)
    Eileen
    Elizabeth
    Elsr
    Evalin
    Fay 8c Ivan
    Gilbetz Lena
    Lucie 8c Victor
    Lucile
    Margaret H.
    Martha 8c Denny(White)
    Bettie 8c Marvin(White)
    Maud
    Mildred 8c Miller
    Nellie
    Ray
    Stephen
    Sue(or Gue)
    Theodosia
    Volunta
    Zane(Vann)
- Incoming Anniversary Cards - 1958 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - By Last Name (A-L) (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Adda, Maurier 8c Marylee
    Alexander,R?
    Anderson, Inez 8c Holger
    Arnau, Prudence
    Arnold, Homer 8c Bessie
    Auden, Doris 8c Ross
    - Black, Betsey 8c Edgar (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Blum, Henry(2)
      Bond, ?
      Bowden, Zelma
      Braegger, Lucie 8c Victor
      Burnette, Mary Lee
      Burritt, Gertrude 8c Richard
    - Cameron, Laura 8c Robert (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Carr, Emma Hassler
      Castro, David 8c E.
      Caviness, ?
      Close, Anne
      Collins, Byron 8c Elfriede
      Collins, Frances 8c R.E.
      Corkey, Bea 8c Joe
      Crymble, Hugh 8c Hannah
    - DeGraff, Margaret (Box 30, Folder 7)
      DeMartine, Mennie
      DelMar, Al & Bee
      DeSzalatuay, ?
      Dowdy, Elizabeth
      DuBois, Kathryn & Howard
    - Eckert, Helen (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Ellsworth W.C.
      Evans, Helene R.
    - Ferber, Fred & Hedwig (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Foss, Phyllis
    - Girod, Carlos (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Glaser, Pearl & Dave
      Glasgow, Signa
      Glidden, Carl & Sophie
      Guernsey, Grace & Roscoe
    - Haviland, Esther (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Harrison, Mary & Dale
      Henry, Florence Stokes
      Herdson, Eileen & Judy
      Hilty, Vany
      Holchier(?), Cecilia
      Hudson, Maud & Walter
      Hughes, Richard
    - Jay, E.,Jr. (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Jones, Arthur & Hazel
    - Kautrouitz(?), Charles (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Kearns, Myra & Bill
      Kelly, Lois
      Kern, Lucy C.
      Kiehl, Mathiene(?)
      Hiehan (?), Marie
      Knox, Daniel
    - Lasky, Charles & Elsie (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Latham, Elvira & Robie
      Leslie, jay & Betty
      Lev/is, Berneita & Charles
      Limberg, Norman & Dorothy
      Lucey, Gordon & Elizabeth
- Incoming Anniversary Cards - 1958 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - By Last Name (M-Z) (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Macalister, May & George
    McClellan, Isabelle & Georg
    McLester, Bertha C.
    Moor, David II. & Irene
    Moore, Hampden & Bessie
    Morse, Daisy & Leighton
    - Newcomb, Abbie (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Newsome, Margaret
      Noble, Paul & Nancy
    - Oliver, Freda & Peter (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Pearce, Lorene V. (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Pendergast, ?
      Petitte, Florence C.F.
    - Rhodes, Bessie & William (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Richards, Grace & Earl
      Roaches
      Rodman, Mae
      Rose, Selma
      Rawill, Ruby E.
      Roulstone, Katharine
    - Sanetakos(?), William (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Schuert(?), Lotte
      Schuldt, Elsn
      Scott, Agnes K.
      Sheridan, Terry & Rosemary
      Skinner, Charles & Ethel
      Smith, Marion & Al
      Smith, Laura
      Stave, Frieda
      Steele, Leslie
      Stickle, Irene & Fred
      Stein, Frank
      Stover, Bob & Shirley
      Stowell, Grace
      Stuart, Helen & Bill
    - Thompson, Anne H. (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Tierney, Frederick
      Tillott, ?
      Tyler, Net & Cecil
    - Vann, Monroe & Madeline (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Vreeland, Wesley & Anne
      Vann, Ruth
    - Ward, Emma F. (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Wentworth, Marion
      Wheeler, F.R.
      Winfree, Lou & Pine
      Winfree, Rieves, Sr.
      Wright, Virginia
      Wyckoff, Christobel
    - Zoylner, Julie (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Incoming Anniversary Cards - 1958 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - First Names Only (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Al & Marguerite
    Blanche & Clarence
    Christine G.
    Elvira
    Emmy Lou
    Everett
    Frances
    Gene & Jessica
    Grover, Emily Ruth & Tina
    Helene R.E.
    Hazle & Paul E.
    Inez & Holger(Anderson)
    Joel, Katherine (Vann)
    Kyle
    LeRoy & May
    Lou
    Louise, Andy & David
    Margie
    Aunt Marie
    Marjorie & Howard
    Mary Virginia & Bob
    May
    Mella, Roy & Mella, Jr.
    Natalie
    Quinta
    Rick
    Rose
    Ruth
    “Ted” & Steve
    Vivian
    Voluita
    Watie Lou
    Zane, Gene, Tina & Ellis(Vann)
    Zelda
  - From Groups: (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Englewood Stamp Club (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Evening Bridge Club (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Hackensack Women’s Philatelic Club (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Polly Wycoff Chapter, D.A.R. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Allen
      Cady
      DeWolt
      Gabel
      Greenlow
      Hooks, Maud M.
      Mazza
      Moore
      Petitte, Florence
      Tierney
      Weeks
  - Incoming Anniversary Telegrams etc. (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Casellas, Munch (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Denny, Collins & Anne (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Denny, Roselind
      Durham, Linna & Hugh
    - Frank, Sndi & Thelma (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Gaston, Carman (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Heath, Betty & Clyde (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Kean, Osmond (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Kreds, Jane & Steven
    - Leon, Gloria & David (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Lopez, Frank & Lia
    - Massey, Helen T. (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Mill, Nancy 8c Bill
      Milroy, ?
    - Northern Valley Chapter AAUN (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Robinson, ? (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Robinson, ?
    - Wickey, May Street(2) (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Wickey, ?
    - Hattie (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Jean
      Mimi & Tom
- Schools, United Methodist Church, Accidents, Illnesses, 90th Birthday, Obituaries, Address Books, Correspondence (Box 31)
  - Wasatch Academy, Mt. Pleasant, Utah (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - “I Lift Up My Eyes to the Hills” (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - “The Old Becomes New: The Centennial of Wasatch Academy, 1875-1975” (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Scarritt College, Nashville, Tennessee (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Financial Report (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Bulletins (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence to Elizabeth from: (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Brentlinger, James(Business Manager), 1974: July 15 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Countryman, Frank(Director of Challange n.d. Finance Campaign) (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Gilbert, Jack(Director of Public Relations and Deferred Giving), 1974: Nov.1,12. 1975: Apr.25; June 4; Nov.3. 1976; Feb.4,24; Apr.30. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Palmer, J. Richard & Dorothy (President), 1973: Oct.24. 1974: Oct.7; Nov.21,29. 1975: Jan.2,8; (Dn.d.; Mar.4,25; May 12. 1976: Nov.3. 1977: Apr.13(to Felix), 14(to Edit* (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Taylor, Jim(Vice-President for Development), 1973: Dec.17. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Westover United Methodist Church, Richmond, Virginia (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Membership certificates (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - (5) cards from study groups (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence to Elizabeth from: (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Alex, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Dot & Jeff, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Liz, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Marjorie, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Allen, Isabella, (2)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Barnes, Bernita, (2)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Burruss, Mrs. Frank(to Edith), 1943: May 15 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Davenport, Hortense, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Dwyer, Evelyn, (2)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Eakin, Mary Ruth, 1963: June 4 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Field, Jewell, 1975: June 10; Aug. 10 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Fridley, Robert, 1973: Dec. 10. 1974: Jan.15 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Harman, Valerie, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Jeffress, Dot, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Jones, Tee & Julius, 1975: Jan.7 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Moore, Ella Clarke, (2)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Paxton, Marian (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Perkins, Perk & Bee, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Taylor, Jack 8c Gwen, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Tucker, Gwendolyn, (2)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Virginia Politics - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - To Elizabeth from: (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Abady, Paula, (2)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Allen, George E., Jr., (l)n.d. 1973: Jan.16 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Bliley, Thomas J., Jr., 1975: June 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Hall, Franklin P., (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Jones, George W., 1973: Jan.16. 1974: Apr.ll. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Millhorn, William, 1975: July. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Parkerson, William F., Jr., 1973: Jan.17 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Willey, Edward E., 1973: Jan.18 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth’s Accident, 1936 - Hospital & Doctor Receipts, Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - To Elizabeth from NAAI Co., 1936: Apr.6; May 26; June 4. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - From Elizabeth to North American Accident Insurance Co.:, 1936: May 28,29. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth’s Accident, 1971, Pennsylvania Turnpike (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence from Elizabeth to: (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - United Hospital, Beaver Falls, Pennsylvania., 197i: July 17; Aug.4. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - 90th Birthday Correspondence, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Poem, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - To Elizabeth from: (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Evelyn & Ray
      DeGraff, Margaret
      Hilty, Everett
      Leonia Democratic Club(Anita Gans)
      Vanderbilt Alumni Association
  - 90th Birthday Greeting Cards (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Illnesses - Elizabeth (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Diagnostic reports (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence to Elizabeth from: (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Baillie, Catherine(Mrs. Arthur C.), (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Denny, Rev. Collins, (l)n.d. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Denny, Mrs. Collins(to Felix), 1934: Mar.16 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Horsley, Dr. J. Shelton(to Felix), 1934”- Mar.16, 21, 23, 27, 30; Apr.5. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Dr. James(to Felix), 1933: Sept.5; Oct.16. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Obituary Notices, Memorial Service (Box 31, Folder 10)